{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Python with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Python?",
      "answers": ["Language", "Module", "Library"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'def'?",
      "answers": ["Func", "Class", "Var"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'list'?",
      "answers": ["Array", "Dict", "Set"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'None'?",
      "answers": ["Null", "Zero", "False"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'for'?",
      "answers": ["Loop", "Cond.", "Var"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'if'?",
      "answers": ["Cond.", "Loop", "Var"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'import'?",
      "answers": ["Include", "Export", "Define"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'print'?",
      "answers": ["Output", "Input", "Error"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'int'?",
      "answers": ["Number", "String", "Bool"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'str'?",
      "answers": ["String", "Number", "Bool"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
